One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Whirl Spider
I don't have time to fight someone as strong as him!
I came here to save Ace!
Gear Second!
We'll face this guy!
Hawk Eye! Do you remember us?!
We've both challenged you before!
But now that we're Newkama, we've powered up!
I don't remember the face of every insect I've crushed.
Almost there! Just a little further!
You're still in range.
T-that hurt...
He cut me!
Hawk Eye jumped into the air?!
Damn you!
Rubber-Rubber...
Jet Bazoo-
That was too close!
If I'd stretched my arms, he'd have cut them off!
You aren't as reckless as I expected.
With just one slash of his sword...
He cut that mountain-sized wall of ice!
S-so this is what the world's mightiest swordsman is capable of.
How freakin' strong is this guy? If he's after Straw Hat, it's all over!
The ice is falling this way!
You want me to team up with you?
Stop talking to me as if we were equals.
You mean you want me to be your underling, right?
Just when I thought Impel Down might have rehabilitated you...
If it had, I wouldn't have gotten out at all.
Sandstorm!
Begone, you damn Flamingo!
And here I thought you'd listen to reason.
As long as I can avoid fighting the marines, this'll all go my way!
No trouble at all!
No trouble! No trouble!
Captain Buggy!
How do you keep getting mixed up in other people's fights like that?!
Now, what will you do?
You are being forced further and further away from your brother!
Damn!
Is this where it ends?
No trouble!
It seems that your fighting power has increased considerably,
but I've already seen through all your tricks.
From this distance there isn't even a ten thousand to one chance I will miss!
No trouble!
Rubber-Rubber...
I'm saved...
Jet Human Shield!
Hey! What're you doing, Straw Hat?!
What?! He was the one who cut you!
Besides, didn't you just say you'd come to help me?
You dumbass! You only hear what you want to hear!
Rubber-Rubber...
Human Shield!
Cut it out!
Unforgivable! You're Hawk Eye, aren't you?!
Special Muggy Ball!
Now get blown away!
Okay, or not.
Do you know why the Muggy Ball is so popular with plumbers?
Why?
All together now... because it goes...
Boom!
Wow. Buggyrific!
Captain Buggy!
Good one!
Thanks, Buggy!
I'll never forget you!
It's not over yet!
Vista! The Old Man ordered us to to keep Ace's brother alive!
Back him up!
Understood. I'm on it!
Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates' Fifth Division, Flower Blade Vista.
5th Division Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates
Flower Blade Vista
Nice to meet you, Hawk Eye Mihawk. So you've heard of me?
It would be strange if I had not.
I'm saved!
Who's that old guy?
It's not a Devil Fruit, or some cheap trick...
Well, whatever. I'm grateful!
One by one, he turns the people around him into his allies.
Keep going, Straw-Hat-boy!
Luffy! You must save your brother!
Move it!
More than anyone else sailing the seas...
that man possesses the most terrifying power.
Ace!
As the execution draws ever closer...
a number of shocking truths have been revealed, one after another.
Over two hundred men did the unthinkable and broke out of the impenetrable Impel Down...
then these infamous, mighty prisoners appeared on the battlefield.
The scene that has unfolded looks like something from a different world.
This truly is an ultimate showdown that will determine the fate of the world!
The people around the world can only hold their breath...
and watch as their futures are decided here.
Fleet Admiral. The preparations are complete.
The ones for the bay coast as well?
Yes. They're all ready.
Huh?
They're preparing to execute him...
They're...
What are they gonna do to Ace?
It's not time yet!
Is the execution gonna start now?
That's impossible! The announced time is still a while off!
Cut the broadcast on all Video Transponder Snails immediately!
For the sake of Absolute Justice, the Navy and the World Government must win this battle at any cost...
regardless of the methods we resort to.
But this might be too much for the weak-willed commoners to handle.
There's no need to show the world the tragedy about to take place.
Old Man...
Hurry!
They really are gonna execute Ace early!
Ace!
In a few hours we will tell the world...
that we were victorious!
That's all they need to know.
Our ships were...
Look at the bay! There's something out there!
They aren't our allies!
The marines must have circled around behind the frozen waves to come from the coast!
They still have men capable of destroying all those ships?
That's...
Who are those guys?!
So those are the Government's human weapons that I heard about...
It's those Kuma-looking guys who were at the Sabaody Archipelago...
There are that many of them?
K-Kuma?
About an hour and a half after the war began...
the Navy gambled everything.
In order to change the flow of the battle...
they plunged into the final phase.
Now, you guys!
I was tired of waiting!
It's finally our turn!
It's the Warlord, Bartholomew Kuma!
Why are there so many of him?
What's going on here?!
It's those things that wreaked havoc here on the Sabaody Archipelago a while back!
Multiple Bartholomew Kumas...
There are even more than there were before!
Main Office! Main Office!
Big news!
Hello? Hello?!
Is that the real one?
I heard rumors about this.
Doctor Vegapunk has been developing a human weapon.
The prototypes were sent out to deal with various incidents.
Are these the human weapons?
Why do they all look like Kuma?
Hey Uncle! This isn't what we planned!
You were supposed to have the pirates surrounded in the bay before we got here,
but they're scattered all over the place!
I figured out the Navy's plan.
Whitebeard
Allied Ships
Marines
First, they intentionally leaked their plans to execute Ace ahead of schedule, so we'd panic.
After that, the enemy would slowly pull back,
drawing the pirates into the bay after them.
At that point, the human weapons would block our retreat and we'd be trapped.
Human Weapons
Checkmate.
So Old Man Whitebeard told us to attack the surrounding ships...
because he saw this coming.
And because of that, we aren't trapped.
We may have lost the left and right flanks,
but we can still trap them between us, from the front and back!
Target the supporting pirate crews first, as planned.
Eliminate everyone who slips past our defenses!
As he says...
Uncle, mind if some of our warships get destroyed, too?
Try to keep it to a minimum.
Roger that.
Let's get going!
I don't know what's going on...!
but you won't take us down that easily!
Oh, crap!
Go, Pacifista!
They got us!
So you don't think twice about sacrificing your own troops.
Don't falter, men!
Push forward into the plaza!
All troops, get off the ice!
Do not let the pirates reach the plaza!
Fall back!
Hurry!
What flower should I make bloom next?
Drive them in, Pacifista!
As if! Take this!
Serves you right!
What's with those things?
It's like they're not even human!
Are they invincible?
The broadcast...
No matter what you do...
we still have the upper hand, Whitebeard.
Once all of the broadcasts have been cut, mobilize the enclosure walls!
Then we'll execute Ace and destroy the enemy all at once!
Understood!
Move it!
Ace is in trouble! I gotta hurry!
Back to where you started from!
Luffy-kun!
Jinbe.
One of the admirals is here...
Dammit!
He's a formidable foe, but we must hurry!
You always knew that strong enemies would stand in your way,
and you decided to come here anyway, right?!
Die, Dragon's son!
Ace's little brother! Are you already tired?
Oh, it's the Division Commanders!
This makes things easier for us!
You can't let one admiral stop you!
Come with us!
Alright! That bastard!
Now's our chance, while the marines are falling back!
Let's break through their defenses!
Oh, now this looks like a tough bunch!
Commander of the Tenth Division, Curiel!
If you try to attack me, I'll simply crush you!
But just staying in this bay makes your doom inevitable anyway!
Ace will die, and with nowhere to run, you'll all be eliminated!
I don't give a damn who wins, but I'd love to see Whitebeard die!
I won't let the Old Man or Ace die!
Let us put our battle on hold, Vista.
It seems that would benefit us both.
We've been ordered to pull back, Smoker-san.
This area is...
Yeah...
I know.
Straw Hat!
Luffy... hurry to your brother!
Have all the broadcasts been cut?!
N-No, wait a little longer.
Please stand by.
We're ready over here!
Hey, move over to the side.
I thought one screen was still broadcasting...
Hey! What's going on here?!
Hmm? Who is that over there?
Oh! Is that... Could it be...
A man who hid his identity until now,
but recently revealed himself as part of the legendary crew...
that sailed with the Pirate King Gold Roger!
Who's that?
Is it really that great pirate, Buggy the Clown?!
Yes, it's me alright!
This thing about me being a legendary pirate...
was supposed to be a secret, but...
W-wait, Captain Buggy! You've got a nosebleed!
Cut! Cut!
Wipe your face!
What the hell is this?!
I'm ordering you to cut this ridiculous broadcast!
We can't advance the plan!
W-Well... a Video Transponder Snail was stolen by the Impel Down escapees!
What?!
Makeup!
Okay!
Alright, time for take two!
Three! Two! One!
Go!
Oh! Is that...
the crewmate of the legendary Roger, and blood brother of Red Hair, one of the Four Emperors...
is that the great pirate, Captain Buggy the Clown?
Yes, it's me alright!
Stop them right now!
That was close!
They've found us! Run!
It appeared that you were cut down by Hawk Eye Mihawk,
but you're still standing! Who could you be?
Who, me?
I'm Buggy!
The legend!
Blow them all to pieces!
What's happening on the battlefield?!
Why were the other broadcasts cut?!
Show us Ace. He's about to be executed!
Show us the Bartholomew Kuma army!
Don't give up!
We can't let ourselves be defeated before we've saved Ace!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Old Man...
Squard... You're all right.
Yeah, I survived, somehow.
I see. I tried contacting you earlier...
How are things going in the bay?
Many of our allies are falling.
If the Navy attacks from behind, it'll work to our advantage.
I'm going, too! We've got no choice but to make one last charge!
You're right.
Squard?
What's he doing there?
Forty-three ships are here to back you up. We all owe you a huge debt.
We'd gladly lay down our lives for the Whitebeard Pirates!
Editing, Sewil
QC, Galaxy 9000, Pepperjack
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking, Halee
Translation, Yibis
Raws, Cruchyroll